<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gabriel W. | Hydroflask App | March 2019</string>

    <string-array name="items">
        <item>18 oz. Standard Mouth</item>
        <item>18 oz. Wide Mouth</item>
        <item>21 oz. Standard Mouth</item>
        <item>24 oz. Standard Mouth</item>
        <item>32 oz. Wide Mouth</item>
        <item>40 oz. Wide Mouth</item>
        <item>64 oz. Wide Mouth</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="prices">
        <item>$29.95</item>
        <item>$29.95</item>
        <item>$32.95</item>
        <item>$34.95</item>
        <item>$39.95</item>
        <item>$42.95</item>
        <item>$59.95</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="descriptions">

        <item>
            Keeping your fluid intake on the upside is easy when you’ve got this portable travel buddy.
            Whether you’re headed to the gym or a quick jaunt across town, you can easily take your refreshment with you.
        </item>

        <item>
            Be ready to take on whatever comes next. Our wide mouth top makes it simple to throw some ice into your
            beverage and hit the road with this easy to carry bottle size. Perfect for morning hikes, afternoon ski
            lessons, or evenings by the campfire, our 18 oz Wide Mouth bottle keeps your ice water ice cold for up to
            24 hours or piping hot up to 12. You can also pair it with our handy Straw Lid and Hydro Flip™ Lid.
        </item>

        <item>
            "Keep life moving with our 21 oz bottle and Standard Flex Cap. It stashes easily into a small shoulder bag, your pack\’s side pocket, or your car cup holder, and holds enough ice cold goodness to keep you going for hours without weighing you down. No wonder it's one of our bestselling water bottles."
        </item>

        <item>
            A little more hydration lets you have a little more fun. From mountain trailheads to morning
            yoga practice, our 24 oz Standard Mouth bottle is just the right size for staying hydrated before,
            during, and after activity. Our largest Standard Mouth available uses TempShield™ double wall vacuum
            insulation to keep your water refreshingly ice cold for up to 24 hours. Plus, it resists
            condensation, so the sides of your bottle stay dry.
        </item>

        <item>
            Big enough for a whole day in the backcountry, our 32 oz Wide Mouth bottle is made with
            professional-grade stainless steel and a wider opening for faster fill. And because it’s
            designed with TempShield™ double wall vacuum insulation, it keeps your ice water refreshingly
            ice cold up to 24 hours and hot drinks hot up to 12. Which means you’ll always have the
            perfect temperature drink.
        </item>

        <item>
            From road trips to endless hours at the beach, our 40 oz Wide Mouth bottle keeps you well-hydrated
            from sun up to sun down. TempShield™ double wall vacuum insulation makes sure your water stays icy cold
            up to 24 hours or your coffee piping hot up to 12.
        </item>

        <item>
            Whether you’re overnighting near Yellowstone or car camping at a festival, our 64 oz Wide Mouth bottle
            makes sure there’s more than enough refreshment to go around. It’s made with professional-grade stainless
            steel and TempShield™ double wall vacuum insulation to keep your water refreshingly ice cold or piping
            hot down to the very last sip.
        </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>
